And this one word
can make or break all our futures.
And anyone who goes against the system
is either incredibly courageous
or super dumb.
RAM CHARAN PANDEY
(SUB INSPECTOR)
And I, Ram Charan Pandey,
have never fallen prey
to this dangerous illusion of courage,
and have never been inclined
to do so either.
Because…
no matter how hard a cockroach works out,
victory always belongs to the shoe.
All that is fine, sir.
But, sir, this Hindi and science lecture,
what does it have to do with my daughter?
It is related, Mandal-babu. It is.
You've been negligent.
That's why your daughter went missing.
Action.
Reaction.
Today is her birthday, sir.
She would have turned 15 today.
Do you know, sir?
She was brilliant at her studies.
Extremely brilliant.
Since her last birthday,
she's been telling her mother
that if she tops this exam,
we have to buy her a TV.
Hello, Mandal-babu, listen to me.
Her results came out yesterday.
She came first.
Now, we have to buy a TV for her.
Right, sir?
We'll have to. Right, sir?
Mandal-babu? Hello? Listen.
This is not the first time
a child has gone missing from Rajiv Camp.
It's been going on for years.
We search for them, bring them back,
and they run away again.
We search for them again
There's so much chasing that I've gone
from being Pandey to being PT Usha.
But nobody's giving me any medals, mister.
But, sir, you can at least lodge an FIR.
You can do that at least, sir.
Can't you at least do that, sir?
So now you're going to tell me
when and how to lodge an FIR?
Why not wear this uniform too
while you're at it?
No, sir. It's all right, sir.
She's 15 years old.
She'll come back, buddy.
She's dead by now, sir, isn't she?
Dead and gone.
Pathak, get some water.
Okay.